[
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Paris?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Washington?",
        "answer": "United States"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is London?",
        "answer": "United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Berlin?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Ottawa?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Rome?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Madrid?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Canberra?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Moscow?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Beijing?",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Ankara?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Seoul?",
        "answer": "South Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Mexico?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Brasilia?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is New Delhi?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Buenos?",
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Pretoria?",
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Tokyo?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Cairo?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Riyadh?",
        "answer": "Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Bangkok?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Amsterdam?",
        "answer": "Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Warsaw?",
        "answer": "Poland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Athens?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Lisbon?",
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Oslo?",
        "answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Helsinki?",
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Copenhagen?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Stockholm?",
        "answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Vienna?",
        "answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Baghdad?",
        "answer": "Iraq"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Abu?",
        "answer": "United Arab Emirates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Islamabad?",
        "answer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Caracas?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Santiago?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Lima?",
        "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Wellington?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Havana?",
        "answer": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the country whose capital is Kigali?",
        "answer": "Rwanda"
    }
]